[{"answer": "I discovered the bodies of my mother, my little sister, and my cousin.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "And when you went home Tony, what did you discover?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I was asked to come down to the precinct.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What then happened?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I really -- at this moment, I really don't even know what I was thinking.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "When you were made to do that, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, when I heard about it, I was extremely overwhelmed.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "When you heard about that or when did you hear about that and what did you expect to then happen?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "You know, I described this case as a perfect storm, everything that could go wrong in a criminal justice situation.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "That there was such a breakdown in the legal process that the medical examiner was not even spoken to by the attorneys?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "It was a nightmare, extremely nightmare of -- and not only was a nightmare, but they had me in the worst, worst maximum security prison in the State of New York which is Attica.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Antonio, what has that been like for you, I mean, bad enough doing present time anyway but to be doing it -- to having falsely convicted of killing your own mother and sister and your little sister's friend, what did that do to you?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "New York air.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "The one thing you've missed most?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Which is pretty cold right now, right?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "It was horrible.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "But describe to me as best you can, how you dealt with it?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Have some New York pizza.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "And when you came out, Shariff, what was the first thing you wanted to do?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, for many years, I felt horrible that I had to do that and that I actually did it.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "How do you cope with that part of this?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, like I told them about a few hours ago, that I have no animosity towards him.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "When you discovered, Antonio, that he had made this revelation to your family, what did you think?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Yeah, I have hope.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you have any hope of finding the real killer now and getting justice for your mother, your sister, and your cousin?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "I say yes, if he's willing.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Shariff, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think we became disconnected about 12 years ago and then we last, Mau, Robin and I gravitated back towards each other a little bit and he's always been twins and the older brother and so there was a real difference.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Is that inevitable when two of your brothers are twins?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I guess it's the difference between being in a group and being brothers in a group or being sisters in a group, you know.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Is it the precious outside forces of fame and so on?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Because it's really about lost love in all the young people.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Why that one?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, we met on the set of Top of the Pops when \"Massachusetts\" was number one and then we had a cup of tea in the canteen of the BBC and then we had a couple in -- and (inaudible) and time stood still.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "How did you met?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Because I think we've just always been in love.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "And how do you manage that because show business is so, this is so listed with broken marriages, how have you managed to sustain such a lasting love do you think?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, I think we've both loved.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "You've never looked to anyone else since she's always in love with you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "IBB: Because I hate looking myself at different ages.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Hard to watch, why?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "It's OK.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And how's the -- how's your voice on that, I mean, how is it compared to what it used to be?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Did people expect you to talk about that?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "But, rather a nostalgia about that, did you and the Beatles hang out much or not?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Your brother Andy?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Is that part of the progress?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Yeah, being around the microphone together.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "What would be your favorite memory or perhaps the big times with your brothers, not the early days (ph)?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "As song writer, beyond anything else and harmonies, you know, there was no great approach.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "ORGAN: What would you like the Bee Gees to stand for, to be remembered for, do you think?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I was the Dolly role and Kenny sang his role.", "docId": "140207pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "So you sang it?", "qSentId": 590}]